As I was coming up with my elevator pitch during my career change,
キャリアを変更する際に 短く自己紹介する場合
I kept thinking about two things.
2 つの事柄を考えました
One, what did I want employers to know about me?
1 つ目は 雇用者は 私に何を求めているかという点です
And two, what was I most proud of?
2 つ目は 私が誇れることは何かということです
I wanted employers to know that I'm passionate about education, but
私は教育に熱心であることを 雇用者に伝えたかったのですが
I wanted to be a software engineer.
なりたかったのはソフトウェア エンジニアでした
I wanted them to know I worked hard to get where I was then and
私はここまでくるのにとても努力したこと そして
that I was worth taking a chance on.
私にかけてみる価値があることを知っていただきたかったのです
Because if I got the job, I would give it everything I had.
仕事を得たら ベストを尽くすことを知っていたからです
So my elevator pitch ended up being something like this.
そのため 私の自己紹介は 次のようになりました
Hi, I'm Chris,
クリスです
a Full Stack Software Engineer who loves building education products.
教育製品を作るのが大好きなフル スタック エンジニア です
I recently developed a web app using AngularJS that let's teachers share
I最近 AngularJS を使って教師が匿名で 勉強用のサンプルを共有できるようにする
student writing samples anonymously.
Web アプリを開発しました
I'd love to combine my passion for
教えることと学ぶことに対する私の情熱を
teaching and learning with my software development skills to
ソフトウェア開発スキルと組み合わせることで 人々のためのパーソナライズされた
continue building personalized learning products for people.
学習製品を 作り続けたいと思っています
My elevator pitch isn't something I recite when I meet someone.
自己紹介は 誰かにあったときに暗唱するものではありません
That would be weird to say hi and then just dive into the pitch, however,
こんにちは といった後で 急に自己紹介を始めるのは不自然なことですが
I could write this pitch as my LinkedIn summary.
自己紹介を LinkedIn のサマリーのように書くことはできます
When I'm talking to someone,
だれかと話す際
I communicate the points in my pitch throughout the conversation.
自己紹介の ポイントを伝えます
Let me show you what that looks like.
どのようなものかお見せしましょう
Pretend in the next video that Trinh's a recruiter and
次のビデオでは トリンが人材採用担当者で
I'm a job-seeker meeting her at a mixer for education start-ups.
私は求職者で 教育新興企業のための親睦会で出会うという設定です